ginside.com 2017-02-03

# Privacy Policy | Traffic Safety Store

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc., Ltd. (“W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc.,” “we” or “us”) is the operator of this website (the “Site”). W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. has implemented this Privacy Policy to provide our clients and other visitors to this website (collectively “Users”) information regarding the collection and use of Information (as defined below) you provide to us or that is otherwise collected when you use this Site, so that you can make an informed decision about your use of the Site.

## Changes

This Privacy Policy was last changed on May 9, 2016.

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. may modify this Privacy Policy at any time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. on the Site. When we post modifications to the Privacy Policy, you can access a copy of the old Privacy Policy ny sending correspondence to info@trafficsafetystore.com

## The Information We Collect

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. collects two types of information about you on this website: User Information and Technical Information. Each of these is defined and explained below, and “Information” refers to anything within the definition of either term.

## User Information

From time-to-time in the course of your use of this Site and any services (the “W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services”) offered on this Site, we may ask you to provide your name, e-mail address, telephone number and other personal identifying information including the information listed below in respect of the traffic safety site (collectively, “User Information”).

You may also provide W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. with names, e-mail addresses and similar information about other individuals such as your employer and colleagues; however, you should only provide information about another person if you have his or her permission to do so. That information will also be treated as User Information for purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Do not supply to us any Information of any person under 13 years of age, as we do not intend to collect information from anyone under 13 or invite them to use this Site. Please check our “ Commitment to Children’s Privacy” below regarding the protection of children.

The information collected on this website (also User Information) includes the following:

  * Your name
  * Your mailing and/or street address
  * Your e-mail
  * Your telephone number for Credit Card company verification purposes

## Technical Information

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. uses cookies and web beacons (also known as ‘clear gifs’ – small single pixel image files that can be used to recognize a user’s navigation through a website) to collect information for record keeping purposes and to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a User’s computer – for more information about these and web beacons, please see www.allaboutcookies.org.

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. uses both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Persistent cookies stay on your computer from one session to the next and enable W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. to recognize you when you return to the Site. In addition, W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. may allow third-party cookies to be placed on your computer. Third-party cookies are similar to W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc.’s own cookies, but they come from servers controlled by third-parties, such as our advertisers and other partners, and are used to collect information about your use of this Site, which information is then used by those third-parties. We do not ordinarily use or otherwise have access to the information contained in these third-party cookies.

You may choose not to receive cookies, whether coming directly from W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. or from third-parties, by following instructions in your web browser’s “help” file, but this may make certain features of the Site inaccessible to you.

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. also collects Users’ IP addresses and basic log file information (such as browser type and language, number of clicks, domain names of web sites visited, pages viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of visits and page views).

This information, including information about cookies, is referred to as “Technical Information” in this policy. W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. uses Technical Information (and may combine it with User Information) to help locate potential problems with our server, improve and customize your experience on the Site and other purposes described in the "How We Use Your Information" section below.

## How We Use Your Information

**User Information:** If you provide User information to us, then we use this information to operate, maintain, and provide the features and functionality of the Site and any W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services.

W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. will contact you using the e-mail address you have provided in the course of providing a particular W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Service you order or request on the Site, including among other things notices required by law.

We may also use your e-mail address to send you other messages if you have agreed to receive them, including advertising, information about changes to W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. features, and special offers. You may subsequently opt out of all of these e-mails, or specified categories of e-mails, by following the “Opt-Out” link found at the bottom of the e-mail or by contacting us at info@Trafficsafetystore.com.

## Technical Information

We use Technical Information, such as Site use data and IP addresses, to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing your preferences and trends.

We may use such information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your current or subsequent visits to the Site; (b) provide customized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (d) diagnose or fix technology problems; (e) use information about you after you log on to the Site for our internal purposes; (f) market our Site to advertisers and other third parties; (g) track users clicking through to this Site from promotional emails and other marketing materials that include links to this Site (h) aggregate general User statistics including demographic and geographic information; and (i) other lawful purposes, so long as your personal identity is not revealed by such use.

As part of this process W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. uses Google Analytics to provide it with aggregated Technical Information about how users interact with the Site, and may set cookies and/or use web beacons for this purpose. The Technical Information gathered by the Google Analytics software (including any personal information about you) will be sent to Google where it will be stored and used by Google in accordance with its Privacy Policy Please review the Google Privacy Policy or contact Google for more information.

## When We Share Information

Except as expressly described below, W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. will not share your Information with advertisers or unaffiliated third parties without first obtaining your express permission.

We may provide Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, subcontractors, vendors and other third-parties with whom we have entered into a co-marketing, partnering or similar cooperative commercial or strategic arrangement, so such parties can, among other things (a) help us to provide or perform W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services and/or process such information on our behalf, (b) use the information to offer greater functionality and enhanced services through the Site or to provide you with additional product and service opportunities and (c) communicate these opportunities to you. When we do this, the recipients of your information are bound by privacy requirements that are at least as restrictive as this Privacy Policy.

We may share Technical Information (such as Site use data) with third parties to assist them in understanding our Site, including Users’ use of our Site and W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services.

The Technical Information provided will not identify you by name, however.

We may release your Information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any applicable laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, law enforcement or regulatory request, or search warrant. We reserve the right to collect and share any information: in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; as appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use or investigate potential or actual violations of the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy; take reasonable precautions against liability; to protect the security or integrity of our Site; or to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc., its affiliates, Users or others.

We may assign or transfer the Information we collect to a third party in the event that W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. is acquired by or merged with a third party entity or in the event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or similar situation.

## Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important and is mandated by applicable law, including U.S. law. For these reasons, W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. does not knowingly collect User Information on the Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site is directed to persons under 13.

If you are under 13 years of age, then you must not use or access the Site at any time or in any manner or provide any information to the Site. If your child has submitted User Information to us, please contact us at info@Trafficsafetystore.com or send a regular letter to 1247 Wrights Lane, Unit E, West Chester, PA 19380 so that we can arrange to remove your child’s User Information from our database.

While we do not collect User Information from persons under 13, User Information may include information about persons under 13, so long as that information is requested in connection with the provision of any W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services and is provided by a parent or other person lawfully permitted to provide such information to us.

## International Users

The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, you are transferring your Information to the United States, and you consent to that transfer.

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES TREAT YOUR INFORMATION IN A MANNER THAT MAY BE SUBSTANTIALLY DIFFERENT FROM, AND LESS PROTECTIVE THAN, THE TREATMENT REQUIRED UNDER THE LAWS OF OTHER COUNTRIES AND JURISDICTIONS. IF YOU DO NOT WANT YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, YOU SHOULD NOT SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH US, OR MAKE USE OF THIS WEBSITE.

TO THE EXTENT ALLOWED BY THE LAW OF THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE ANY RIGHT YOU MAY HAVE TO REQUIRE US TO TREAT YOUR IDENTIFYING INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF ANY COUNTRY OR JURISDICTION OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES. HOWEVER, THE FOREGOING WAIVER MAY NOT BE LEGALLY BINDING IN SOME COUNTRIES. TO THE EXTENT IT IS NOT LEGALLY BINDING IN THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, THIS FOREGOING WAIVER DOES NOT APPLY TO YOU.

## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit User Information to the Site, in which case you may not be able to utilize all of the features and functionality of this Site and W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. may not be able to provide certain Products and Services to you.

## Passwords

We may assign to you, or ask you to select, a password and username in connection with your use of certain features of the Site or the provision of W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services to you.

You can change your password and username at any time by going to [this link](https://www.trafficsafetystore.com/account/forgotpassword). If we assign a password to you, you should change that password as soon as possible to ensure that your password is something you will remember and that is unique to you. You acknowledge that you are responsible for protecting your password and ensuring that you do not disclose your password to others.

If your password is disclosed to others, they will be able to access your User Information and otherwise interfere with your use of this Site and any W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. Products and Services. If you become aware that your password has been improperly disclosed or used by others, you should immediately change your password. Contact us at info@Trafficsafetystore.com if you believe someone is, or has been, using your username or password for unlawful or improper purposes.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

We have implemented technical and organizational measures designed to secure your Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or access and use your Information for improper purposes. You acknowledge that you provide your User Information at your own risk.

## Compromise of Your Information

In the event that your Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. will promptly notify you in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Notification Procedures

It is W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc.’s policy to provide notifications relating to security breaches, as well as other notifications required by law, via e-mail notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notices on our Site, as determined by W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. in its sole discretion. Similarly, to the extent you have authorized us to do so, we provide other notifications to Users using the same alternative means. W.L. Snook & Associates, Inc. reserves the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications required by law to our Users, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Contact Information

Please contact us at info@Trafficsafetystore.com with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the Site.
